There is a "je ne sais quoi" in the air
Summer Villa is a romance, comedy, tv movie film directed by Pat Kiely.
Although a successful romance novelist, Terry Russell
hasn't had luck in her own love life.
After a disastrous first date with cocky, hot-shot New York chef Matthew Everston, she retreats to her friend's
French villa for the summer to finish her latest novel, with her reluctant teenage daughter in tow.
Terry Russell, played by Hilarie Burton.
Abby Russell, played by Emorphia Margaritis.
Matthew Everston, played by Victor Webster.
Leslie Everston, played by Cristina Rosato.
Dianne, played by Brittany Drisdelle.
René-Claude, played by Joseph Bellerose.
Malena Villa is an Argentine actress and singer-songwriter.
The film explores themes of villa, summer, chef, novelist, hallmark.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.